var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "وَأَخَّرَ",
        "answer": "and kept back",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wa-akhara",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةَ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirata",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "So when",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "345",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "346",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "To",
        "pcklId": "717",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "Towards",
        "pcklId": "718",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "To",
        "pcklId": "719",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "720",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَامَهُ",
        "answer": "(to) what is before him",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "amāmahu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأُنْثَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the female",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wal-unthā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "[the] man",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "[the] man",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "[the] man",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "[the] man",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "[The] man",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِهِ",
        "answer": "his family",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "ahlihi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَرِقَ",
        "answer": "is dazzled",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bariqa",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَاسِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) distorted",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bāsiratun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَصَرُ",
        "answer": "the vision",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-baṣaru",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصِيرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) a witness",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "baṣīratun",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَلَغَتِ",
        "answer": "it reaches",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "balaghati",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنَانَهُ",
        "answer": "his fingertips",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "banānahu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيَانَهُ",
        "answer": "(is) its explanation",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "bayānahu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاتَّبِعْ",
        "answer": "then follow",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "fa-ittabiʿ",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّرَاقِيَ",
        "answer": "the collar bones",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-tarāqiya",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُتْرَكَ",
        "answer": "he will be left",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yut'raka",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "Then made",
        "pcklId": "326",
        "tlit": "fajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْمَعَ",
        "answer": "We will assemble",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "najmaʿa",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجُمِعَ",
        "answer": "And are joined",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wajumiʿa",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمْعَهُ",
        "answer": "(is) its collection",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "jamʿahu",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحِبُّونَ",
        "answer": "you love",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "tuḥibbūna",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحَرِّكْ",
        "answer": "move",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tuḥarrik",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَحْسَبُ",
        "answer": "Does think",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "ayaḥsabu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَحْسَبُ",
        "answer": "Does think",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ayaḥsabu",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْيِيَ",
        "answer": "give life",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'yiya",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخَسَفَ",
        "answer": "And becomes dark",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wakhasafa",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَخَلَقَ",
        "answer": "then He created",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "fakhalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذَّكَرَ",
        "answer": "(the) male",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "l-dhakara",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَهَبَ",
        "answer": "he went",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "dhahaba",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "919",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهَا",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "920",
        "tlit": "rabbihā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "921",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَاقٍ",
        "answer": "(will) cure",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "rāqin",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "Desires",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّوْجَيْنِ",
        "answer": "two kinds",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-zawjayni",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْأَلُ",
        "answer": "He asks",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "yasalu",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُدًى",
        "answer": "neglected",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sudan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاقُ",
        "answer": "the leg",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-sāqu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالسَّاقِ",
        "answer": "about the leg",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bil-sāqi",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَسَاقُ",
        "answer": "(will be) the driving",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-masāqu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُسَوِّيَ",
        "answer": "We can restore",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "nusawwiya",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَوَّىٰ",
        "answer": "and proportioned",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fasawwā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّمْسُ",
        "answer": "the sun",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-shamsu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدَّقَ",
        "answer": "he accepted (the) truth",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ṣaddaqa",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَلَّىٰ",
        "answer": "he prayed",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ṣallā",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَظُنُّ",
        "answer": "Thinking",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "taẓunnu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظَنَّ",
        "answer": "And he is certain",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "waẓanna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَعْجَلَ",
        "answer": "to hasten",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "litaʿjala",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَاجِلَةَ",
        "answer": "the immediate",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-ʿājilata",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعَاذِيرَهُ",
        "answer": "his excuses",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "maʿādhīrahu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِظَامَهُ",
        "answer": "his bones",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "ʿiẓāmahu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَقَةً",
        "answer": "a clinging substance",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ʿalaqatan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَفْجُرَ",
        "answer": "to give (the) lie",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "liyafjura",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَفَرُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the escape",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-mafaru",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفِرَاقُ",
        "answer": "(is) the parting",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "l-firāqu",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُفْعَلَ",
        "answer": "will be done",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "yuf'ʿala",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاقِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "backbreaking",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "fāqiratun",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَادِرِينَ",
        "answer": "(We are) Able",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "qādirīna",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقَادِرٍ",
        "answer": "(He) Able",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "biqādirin",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَّمَ",
        "answer": "he sent forth",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "qaddama",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرَأْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We have recited it",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "qaranāhu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُرْآنَهُ",
        "answer": "and its recitation",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "waqur'ānahu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرْآنَهُ",
        "answer": "its recitation",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "qur'ānahu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْتَقَرُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the place of rest",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-mus'taqaru",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُقْسِمُ",
        "answer": "I swear",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "uq'simu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُقْسِمُ",
        "answer": "I swear",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "uq'simu",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَمَرُ",
        "answer": "the moon",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-qamaru",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقَمَرُ",
        "answer": "and the moon",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wal-qamaru",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "Will say",
        "pcklId": "1596",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقِيلَ",
        "answer": "And it is said",
        "pcklId": "1597",
        "tlit": "waqīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "556",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "557",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "he denied",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "kadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُ",
        "answer": "he",
        "pcklId": "1325",
        "tlit": "yaku",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "he was",
        "pcklId": "1326",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِسَانَكَ",
        "answer": "your tongue",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "lisānaka",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْتَفَّتِ",
        "answer": "And is wound",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-tafati",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "he presents",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "alqā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّوَّامَةِ",
        "answer": "self-accusing",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-lawāmati",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Is not",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "alaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَمَطَّىٰ",
        "answer": "swaggering",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yatamaṭṭā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُمْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "emitted",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yum'nā",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنِيٍّ",
        "answer": "semen",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "maniyyin",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتَىٰ",
        "answer": "(to) the dead",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "l-mawtā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَبَّأُ",
        "answer": "Will be informed",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yunabba-u",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَاضِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) radiant",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "nāḍiratun",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُطْفَةً",
        "answer": "a semen-drop",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "nuṭ'fatan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَاظِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "looking",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "nāẓiratun",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالنَّفْسِ",
        "answer": "by the soul",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "tlit": "bil-nafsi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسِهِ",
        "answer": "himself",
        "pcklId": "287",
        "tlit": "nafsihi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهٌ",
        "answer": "Faces",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "wujūhun",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَوُجُوهٌ",
        "answer": "And faces",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "wawujūhun",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَذَرُونَ",
        "answer": "And leave",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "watadharūna",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَرَ",
        "answer": "refuge",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wazara",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَوَلَّىٰ",
        "answer": "and turned away",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "watawallā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "Woe",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "awlā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَوْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "and woe",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "fa-awlā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "woe",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "awlā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَوْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "and woe",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "fa-awlā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَوْمِ",
        "answer": "by (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "304",
        "tlit": "biyawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Day",
        "pcklId": "305",
        "tlit": "yawmu",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "75",
        "ayah": "6"
    }
]; 
export default words;